Mia Hossain

Competitive Programmer

Mirzapur, 3331 Habigonj, Bangladesh

+8801710476123

in Mia Hossain

nossain95

▶ Portfolio



SUMMARY

As a problem solver and a competitive programmer, I'm enthusiastic to contribute to the team's work with my skills and experiences as well as through acquiring more in the future and applying them properly for the advantages of the company's development.

EDUCATION

B.Sc in CSE, International Islamic University Chittagong(IIUC)

2017 - 2021

CGPA: 3.72 out of 4

HSC, Kazi Mohammad Shafiqul Islamc College, Brahmanbaria, Bangladesh

2012 - 2014

CGPA: 4.60 out of 5.00

SSC, Jagadishpur J.C High School, Itakhola, Madhabpur, Habiqonj, Sylhet

2010 - 2012

CGPA: 4.38 out of 5

ONLINE JUDGE PROFILES

• CODECHEF:

User name: hossain_95 ∂, Solved: 245+ problems Participated: 77+ contests, Highest Rating: 1741

• CODEFORCES:

User name: hossain95 ∅, Solved: 1370+ problems Participated: 165+ contests, Highest Rating: 1372

• ATCODER:

User name: hossain95 ⊘, Solved: 190+ problems Participated: 55+ contests, Highest Rating: 637

• HACKEREARTH:

User name: hossain95 $\mathscr O$, Solved: 50+ problems Participated: 26+ contests, Highest Rating: 1551

• LEETCODE:

User name: hossain95 Ø, Highest Rating: 1527

• UVA:

User name: MiaHossain ${\mathscr O}$, Solved: 200+ problems

• LIGHTOJ:

User name: hossain95 Ø, Solved 30+ problems

• Stopstalk: hossain_iiuc ∂

Problems **solved 1900+**, Participated in **330+ online contests**.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Trainer, *Competitive Programming, IIUC* 2020 – present

TRAINING AND WORKSHOP

Advanced Competitive Programming Camp,

IIUC

2020 - 2021

Topic: Advance Data-Structure and Algorithms.

Training duration: 6 months.

Trainer: Md Mahamudur Rahaman Sajib (ACM ICPC

World Finalist 2020)

Advanced Competitive Programming,

Dev Skill

2020

Topic: Advance Data-Structure and Algorithms.

Training duration: 6 months.

Trainer: Md Mahamudur Rahaman Sajib (ACM ICPC

World Finalist 2020)

Competitive Programming workshop, //UC

2019

Topic: Competitive Programming

Training duration: 2 days

Workshop on "Hands on Machine Leaning for Research", //UC

2019

From this workshop, we learned the necessary tools, techniques, and algorithms for machine learning.

ORGANISATIONS

Computer Club, International Islamic University Chittagong, Executive

INTERESTS

 Problem solving, Web development, Cooking, travelling.

SKILLS

C/C++

Java

Python

Data Structures & Algorithms

JavaScript

Web Development

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

JQuery

Json

API MYSQL

Operating System

Linux and Windows

Machine Learning

PROJECTS

competitive-programmer-profile *⊗* Feature:

- 1. User profile (codefoces, codechef, atcoder)
- 2. Compare between Two user profiles (codeforces)
- 3. University user's standing (running and previous contest)
- 4. Country user's standing (running and previous contest)
- 5. Total Problem solved in contest time (with problem link)
- 6. Total Problem solved (with problem link)
- 7. Unsolved Problem (with problem link)
- 8. Common Problem solved between two user's (with problem link)

Tools and Language:

Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, BootStrap, API etc.